Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Photographs, 1810-2006 UA.Photos
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 50th Reunion Homecoming Reception, CAS '49, October 2, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Erie Event, September 29, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- CAS 1936 Reunion, unknown (Box 3, Folder 89)
- CAS 1941 Reunion #1, unknown (Box 3, Folder 90)
- CAS 1941 Reunion #2, unknown (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Hillman Library (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Cathedral of Learning #1 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Spotlight on the Sciences-Sampler-the Quality of Human Life, November 2, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- CAS-928 Cathedral of Learning, unknown (Box 3, Folder 95)
- CAS Annual Fund Progress Report-Fall 1993 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- UA Miscellaneous Photos #1 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- UA Miscellaneous Photos #2 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- UA Miscellaneous Photos #3 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- UA Miscellaneous Photos #4 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- CAS 1943 and 1944 Reunion, unknown (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Letter to Dean Briscoe, unknown (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Portraits (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Chemistry Dept. (Box 3, Folder 104)
- QUEST Summer Program--Students-chemistry Experiment-mid 90s, unknown (Box 3, Folder 105)
- QUEST/STEP Summer 95-End of Program Celebration-August, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Commencement (Box 3, Folder 107)
- ARC, Ariel Burgos(L) and Gregory Allen (R), 2003? (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Gail Austin, Former ARC Director, April 2010 (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Helen Faison Scholarship Presentation, unknown (Box 3, Folder 110)
- 1996 Summer Programs-Closing Ceremony STEP/QUEST (Box 3, Folder 111)
- QUEST/STEP Summer move-in Towers Lobby, June 19, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 112)
- UCEP End of Year Celebration-27th Floor Cathedral, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 113)
- UCEP Annual Grad Celebration, April 27, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Helen Faison Scholarship, October 25, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Summer Programs #1-mid 90s thru early 2000s (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Summer Programs #2-mid 90s thru early 2000s (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Summer Programs #3-95-97 (Box 3, Folder 118)
- SAC and SAB Folder #1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- SAC and SAB Folder #2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- SAC and SAB Folder #3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- SAC and SAB Folder #4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- SAC and SAB Folder #5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- SAC and SAB Folder #6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Hospitals (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Benefits Fair (Box 4, Folder 8)
- UN Ambassadors Visit Pitt, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Schools of Health Sciences/Salk Hall (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Langley Hall Explosion, unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pgh. Tuberculosis League/The Posvars (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Board Meetings, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Commencement 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Commencement: May 1980, 1985, May 1973, 1972, 1972, 1973, 1980, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Senate Council, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Pitt Professors, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- IUP Union (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Pitt Aerial View (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Job Fair WPU Ballroom, January 23, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Debate Team Coach, January 26, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Pitt Maintenance, February 1, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Nordy, February 9, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Open House, February 10, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Demonstration, February 18, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- School of Library and Information Sciences, April 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Retirees Reception, June 16, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- President of Turkey, April 21, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Pitt Protests, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Pitt Stadium Panther Glass Painting, July 24, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Pitt Professors, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Syria Mosque, unknown (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Board of Trustees, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- University Senate Meetings, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Chancellors Awards and Teachers Awards, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Provost and Vice Provost Candidates, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Demo Lessons, January 20, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Censorship, February 15, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Founders Day Symposium, February 25, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Honors Convocation, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Candice Hoke Tenure Protest, April 19, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Commencement, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Allen Hall, May ??, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Pitt-Greensburg Campus (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Francophone, unknown (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Yearbook Photo Negatives, unknown (Box 4, Folder 46)
- UCEP Welcome Picnic Fall 98, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Spring 97 UCEP End of Year Celebration-Pitt Club, April 25, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Fall 97 Welcome Picnic-UCEP/QUEST/STEP-Cathedral Lawn, August ??, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- UCEP/Check-in Summer 96-Towers Lobby, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- QUEST/STEP Kickoff Picnic, June ??, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- UCEP Graduation-Old Pitt Club (new ARC), April 24, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- UCEP Recognition Program-WPU, March 25, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- UCEP End of Year Student Celebration, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- UCEP Summer Programs Picnic, Cathedral Lawn, June ??, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- UCEP Offices-unknown event between 94 and 98-2717 CL (Box 4, Folder 56)
- QUEST Group Presentations-WPU Assembly Room-mid to late 90s, unknown (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Summer Programs Event (Box 4, Folder 58)
- UCEP Summer Photos-Group Photos-mid to late 90s Outside Posvar Hall, unknown (Box 4, Folder 59)
- UCEP-1990s Miscellaneous, unknown (Box 4, Folder 60)
- UCEP 1996 Summer Programs Closing Ceremony-WPU Ballroom (Box 4, Folder 61)
- UCEP Holiday Party December-mid 90s-2717 CL (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Student Life Circa Early 1970s, unknown (Box 4, Folder 63)
- UCEP Christmas Party and Open House, December 1998 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- UCEP End of Year Celebration, April ??, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- 1999 Posvar Hall Retention/Advising Conference/Workshop (Box 4, Folder 66)
- UCEP-Holiday Party, December 1995 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- QUEST/STEP Summer 95 End of Program Celebration-August/QUEST Summer Check-in/UCEP Opening Picnic Summer 95, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- UCEP 92-95 UCEP Offices 2717 CL, unknown (Box 4, Folder 69)
- UCEP End of Year Student Celebration (Box 4, Folder 70)
- UCEP Graduation, April 1, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- UCEP Staff End of Year Party, 2000? (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Christmas Holiday Open House-UCEP Offices-Cathedral 95 or 96, unknown (Box 4, Folder 73)
- UCEP Polaroids, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 74)